// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Don't ..... me. I'll be back late.",
    answer: "D) wait for",
    options: [
      "A) hope for",
      "B) waiting for",
      "C) expect",
      "D) wait for",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The lady ..... in the corner is my aunt.",
    answer: "D) sitting",
    options: [
      "A) whose",
      "B) is sitting",
      "C) sits",
      "D) sitting",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "FIND THE CORRECT ANSWER",
    answer: "A) He used to play chess very often",
    options: [
      "A) He used to play chess very often",
      "B) He uses play chess very often",
      "C) He was played chess very often",
      "D) He didn't playing chess very often",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "He doesn't like ..... what to do.",
    answer: "D) being told",
    options: [
      "A) told",
      "B) said",
      "C) having said",
      "D) being told",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "I ..... it doesn't rain tomorrow, I'm going for a picnic.",
    answer: "C) hope",
    options: [
      "A) wait",
      "B) expect",
      "C) hope",
      "D) wish",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "I thought you .....",
    answer: "B) were coming to the party",
    options: [
      "A) will come to the party",
      "B) were coming to the party",
      "C) come to the party",
      "D) have come to the party",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "He remembers being ..... to the fair as a child.",
    answer: "C) taken",
    options: [
      "A) visited",
      "B) brought",
      "C) taken",
      "D) shown",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Finishing a course is always .....",
    answer: "A) satisfying",
    options: [
      "A) satisfying",
      "B) satisfaction",
      "C) satisfies",
      "D) satisfied",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "She worked hard yesterday and ..... finish everything.",
    answer: "B) was able to",
    options: [
      "A) can",
      "B) was able to",
      "C) is hard",
      "D) let",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "FIND THE CORRECT ANSWER",
    answer: "B) Ask her when the food will be ready",
    options: [
      "A) Ask her when will be ready the food",
      "B) Ask her when the food will be ready",
      "C) Ask herv when will the food ready be",
      "D) Ask her when will be the food ready",
    ]
  },

];